Hi friends this is Venkatesh Rao
everyone is fine friends today we have a
topic about work from home job
in Lombard
before we go to the full details about this company if anyone has subscribed to our channel then
subscribe like share
these are what we are telling you every day on
our youtube channel through latest notifications if
you have
subscribed these will
come to you every day
okay my friends if you go to the topic the
date comes on February 24th morning 9:30
am to evening 5:30 pm the venue of
this interview is
ICI Lombard General Insurance
Company 6th floor Summit Building
Gatmi Nagar Lucknow okay if you go to this address
we will be
conducting interviews for more details
we need
790 375837
this number we can call  If they contact you, they will
tell you the full details.
Okay, friends, they have
given us the venue like this. The interviews will be held on February 24 from
9:30 am to
5:30 pm.
Experience
should be one to four years of experience. Salary is 25 to 5
lakhs, which means 250,000 to 5 lakhs per
year.
This is a remote job, which means work from
home. Where will it be in the office? It
means it will be in Lucknow. We will
also be given a job in Lucknow. KRA comes.
KRA job description comes. KRA is a
recruiting agent and providing
regular training and for
selling insurance policies. After that,
achieve the targets assigned and
maintain the round sound relations with the
clients and agents. Achieve assigned
PMS targets through intermediaries
mapped.  Licensing Tracking and
Activation of the
Agents Maintain Sound
Relationships with the
Agents and Providing Regular
Product and Process Training to Them In
this way, if we want,
we are given training from time to time. According to the training, we have
targets to achieve. According to those targets,
we go to the agents and the agents
give us their license and they tell us that we should not have it from time to time from their agents. In
this way, they give us
knowledge and these responsibilities.
We get this job and a role in the job and they
give us as a sales head.
B to C Industry Type comes and
Insurance Department Sales
Business Development Employment Type
comes and it is full time and it is permanent. The
role category is Retail and B to C.
Our education can be any degree,
any degree we have.
If you read this, you can qualify for this job.
Okay friends. In this
way, we have a work from home job in ICI Lombard, a general
insurance company.
Okay friends. Thank you so much. If
you
want more such information, subscribe to our channel.
Like, share, and
subscribe. Every day,
we will
update our channel regarding jobs through the latest notification.
You can see it and
attend interviews.
Thank you so much. All the best friends.